(Sheldon:)So... they're requesting
(Sheldon:)that the white boy play
the funky music, yes?
(Amy:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)And this music we're listening
to right now is funky as well?
(Sheldon:)Sure.
(Sheldon:)Let me ask you this.
(Amy:)Do you think
(Sheldon:)this song is the music
the white boy ultimately plays?
(Leonard:)It could be.
(Sheldon:)So it's like the musical
equivalent of Russell's Paradox,
(Sheldon:)the question of whether
the set of all sets
(Sheldon:)that don't contain themselves
as members contains itself?
(Leonard:)Exactly.
Well...
(Sheldon:)then I hate it.
(Sheldon:)Music should just be fun.
(music stops)
(Leonard:)Making great time.
(Leonard:)Gonna be there pretty early.
(Sheldon:)Will our hotel room
be ready?
(Leonard:)I doubt it.
(Sheldon:)Aren't you worried
that sitting in the lobby